<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<ArrayOfJoke xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Joke>
    <Text>It's hard to explain puns to kleptomaniacs because they always take things literally.</Text>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <Text>I went on a once in a lifetime holiday. Never again.</Text>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <Text>Shout out to the people who want to know what the opposite of in is.</Text>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <Text>My granddad has the heart of a lion and a life time ban from the Edinburgh zoo.</Text>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <Text>I can't stand being in a wheelchair.</Text>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <Text>What's the best thing about Switzerland? I don't know, but their flag is a huge plus.</Text>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <Text>A Buddhish walks up to a hotdog stand and says, "Make ne one with everything"</Text>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <Text>I'm addicted to brake fluid, but I can stop whenever I want.</Text>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <Text>This is your captain speaking, AND THIS IS YOUR CAPTAIN SHOUTING</Text>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <Text>Velcro is a complete rip-off</Text>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <Text>A plateau is the highest form of flattery</Text>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <Text>Rick Astley will let you borrow any movie from his Pixar collection, except one. He's never gonna give you up.</Text>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <Text>Dwarfs and midgets have very little in common.</Text>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <Text>Why is 6 afraid of 7? Because 7 is a registered 6 offender.</Text> </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <Text>Don't you hate it when people answer their own question? I do. </Text>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <Text>I told my doctor that I broke my arm in two places. He told me to stop going to those places. </Text>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <Text>What do you call it when Batman skips church? Christian Bale.</Text>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <Text>What's orange and sound like a parrot? A carrot.</Text>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <Text>A cannibal passed his brother in the woods.</Text>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <Text>What'e E.T. short for? Because he's only got little legs.</Text>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <Text>A photon is going through airport security. The TSA agent asks if he has any luggage. The photon says, “No, I’m traveling light.”</Text>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <Text> Why do engineers confuse Halloween and Christmas? Because Oct 31 = Dec 25
    </Text>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <Text>
      A logician’s wife is having a baby. The doctor immediately hands the newborn to the dad. His wife asks impatiently: “So, is it a boy or a girl?” The logician replies: “Yes.”
    </Text>
  </Joke>
  <Joke>
    <Text>
      Einstein, Newton and Pascal are playing hide and go seek. It’s Einstein’s turn to count so he covers his eyes and starts counting to ten. Pascal runs off and hides. Newton draws a one meter by one meter square on the ground in front of Einstein then stands in the middle of it. Einstein reaches ten and uncovers his eyes. He sees Newton immediately and exclaims, ”Newton! I found you! You’re it!”  Newton smiles and says “You didn’t find me, you found a Newton over a square meter. You found Pascal!”
    </Text>
  </Joke>
</ArrayOfJoke>
